♪ Penny Lane, there is a barber
showing photographs ♪
♪ Of every head
he's had the pleasure to know ♪
♪ And all the people
that come and go ♪
♪ Stop and say, "Hello" ♪
♪ On the corner is a banker
with a motorcar ♪
♪ The little children laugh
at him behind his back ♪
♪ And the banker
never wears a Mac ♪
♪ In the pouring rain ♪
♪ Very strange ♪
♪ Penny Lane is in my ears
and in my eyes ♪
♪ Wet beneath
the blue suburban skies ♪
♪ I sit and meanwhile back ♪
♪ In Penny Lane there is
a fireman with an hourglass ♪
♪ And in his pocket
is a portrait of the Queen ♪
♪ He likes to keep
his fire engine clean ♪
♪ It's a clean machine ♪
[BELL CLANGING]
[TRUMPET SOLO]
♪ Penny Lane is in my ears
and in my eyes ♪
♪ A four of fish
and finger pies ♪
♪ In summer, meanwhile back ♪
♪ Behind the shelter in
the middle of the roundabout ♪
♪ A pretty nurse is selling
poppies from a tray ♪
♪ And though she feels
as if she's in a play ♪
♪ She is anyway ♪
♪ Penny Lane, the barber
shaves another customer ♪
♪ We see the banker sitting
waiting for a trim ♪
♪ And then,
the fireman rushes in ♪
♪ From the pouring rain ♪
♪ Very strange ♪
♪ Penny Lane is in my ears
and in my eyes ♪
♪ There beneath
the blue suburban skies ♪
♪ I sit and meanwhile back ♪
♪ Penny Lane is in my ears
and in my eyes ♪
♪ There beneath
the blue suburban skies ♪
♪ Penny Lane ♪
[♪♪♪]